TOM MANN

LEEDS, UK

CONTACT

07437012778

thomasemann4@gmail.com

PROFILE

I have a background in music, both in performance and in industry studies, having recently finished my MA thesis on music and the platform economy. I also have experience with social media, radio, and in kitchens. Outside of work, I am teaching myself to code.

EDUCATION

Masters in Popular Music **Practice**

BIMM Bristol 2020-2021

Grade - Distinction

BA Professional Musicianship

BIMM Bristol

2016-2019

SKILLS

Time management

Problem solving

Communication

Creativity

Quick learner

Logic Pro X

Photoshop

Premiere Pro

Basic HTML, CSS, JavaScript

EXPERIENCE

FRONT OF HOUSE / BREAKFAST COOK

Doof Cafe, North Wales | 2015 - 2016

· A mixed role which included taking orders and working in the kitchen cooking simple all day breakfasts.

FRONT OF HOUSE / BARMAN

We Three Loggerheads, North Wales | July 2019 - Sept 2020

- Front of house work at a busy, tourist-heavy pub in North Wales.
- Taking orders, working the bar, etc.

KITCHEN ASSISTANT

The Strawberry Thief | May 2021 - August 2021

- Started role as a KP, before supporting a head chef in a small kitchen.
- Plating of dishes to a high standard.
- Being solely responsible for cooking in the kitchen on quiet nights.